<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LearnCamp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="madam">Madam John Imoh</string>
    <string name="banker">Banker</string>
    <string name="changeable">changeable</string>
    <string name="bankers">Our company is looking to fill the role of bank. If you are looking for an exciting place to work, please take a look at the list of qualifications below. Responsibilities for bank Issues and receives in-house portable banks Works a bank supporting arena concession stands Work in different departments/divisions of the Bank to gain perspective, learn processes and procedures, and build knowledge base Participate in departmental/division meetings which may include speaking and/or preparing written materials Compile and analyze data related to area of training Attend in-house training tailored to specific positions including but not limited to Teller and Personal Banker training and supervisory training Attend business development and other bank related functions Establishes vision, strategies, and goals for area of responsibility in alignment with enterprise and department objectives Provides leadership, planning, and direction regarding work and resources to meet established goals Responsible for creating a working environment that fosters superior customer service, teamwork, job enrichment, and productivity Qualifications for bank Must be action-oriented with a great sense of customer focus Basic skills in computer terminal and personal computer operation Performs (and at times, prepares, reviews and leads) special reviews, investigations, monitoring activities, and work for external auditors and/or regulators Bachelor\'s degree or six years of relevant experience in lieu of a degree Communication and customer service skills in order to deal professionally, effectively, and courteously with coworkers, donors, and the general public Analytical skills necessary to perform calculations, and operate donor collection equipment, computers and printers</string>
    <string name="doctor">A Doctor, or Physician, is responsible for promoting the health and safety of their patients by providing proactive treatment and diagnoses. Their duties include speaking with patients to address their health concerns, conducting physical examinations to ensure their patients’ health and administering vaccinations for common illnesses or allergies.  Are you a Job Seeker? Find Jobs  Doctor duties and responsibilities The main duties and responsibilities a Doctor must fulfill in order to do their job well and provide the best care for each of their patients include:  Maintain regularly updated patient medical records that document all evaluations, medications, treatments, allergies, test results and other records Evaluate a patient’s symptoms and determine the most appropriate course of treatment to address them Prescribe medications in compliance with state and federal statutes and inform patients of all possible risks, complications and interference with other medications they may be taking Supervise and evaluate Medical Assistants to ensure full compliance with regulations and make sure that the current care program is as effective as possible Consult patients on topics such as proper nutrition, fitness and hygiene to assist them in making informed decisions and taking good care of their health</string>
    <string name="lawyer">Lawyer Job Description Template We are looking to hire a lawyer with brilliant research and analytical skills. Lawyers are expected to display sound judgment and decision-making with outstanding problem-solving and communication skills.  To ensure success, lawyers should be determined, professional and well informed with a keen interest in upholding the law while protecting a client’s rights. Top candidates will display natural leadership qualities with fantastic interpersonal, written and public speaking skills.  Lawyer Responsibilities: Monitor legal risk in documentation and giving guidance on the acceptable assumption of risk. Interpret laws, rulings and regulations for natural and juristic persons. Conduct legal research and gather evidence. Ensure that appropriate approvals are in place before documents are executed. Explain the law and give legal advice. Offer legal representation at arbitration or mediation hearings. Draft, review and manage wills, trusts, estates, contracts and deeds. Manage regulatory and compliance-related services. Facilitate innovative solutions to client problems. Offer legal representation to clients in court proceedings on civil or criminal matters. Manage and oversee paralegals and legal assistants. Prepare pleadings, notices and make appearances in court.</string>
    <string name="engineer">Engineer Job Description: Top Duties and Qualifications An Engineer, or Senior Engineer, uses math and science to solve different technical problems. Their main duties include developing new products for companies or individuals to use, providing maintenance to current products to enhance use and designing new machines to improve an organization’s efficiencies.  Are you a Job Seeker? Find Jobs  Engineer duties and responsibilities An Engineer’s duties and responsibilities ensure the safety and effectiveness of a process, system or product. Engineers work within a team and must be able to cooperate with other coworkers to ensure the success of a project. Effective communication plays a role between Engineers, customers and businesses. Other engineer responsibilities include:  Making plans using detailed drawings  Preparing estimates and budgets Creating accurate project specifications Designing engineering experiments Creating technical reports for customers Completing regulatory documents concerning safety issues Finishing projects on time and within budget Communicating with clients and coworkers about analysis results</string>
    <string name="developer">Job brief We are looking for a Software Developer to build and implement functional programs. You will work with other Developers and Product Managers throughout the software development life cycle.  In this role, you should be a team player with a keen eye for detail and problem-solving skills. If you also have experience in Agile frameworks and popular coding languages (e.g. JavaScript), we’d like to meet you.  Your goal will be to build efficient programs and systems that serve user needs.  Responsibilities Work with developers to design algorithms and flowcharts Produce clean, efficient code based on specifications Integrate software components and third-party programs Verify and deploy programs and systems Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing software Gather and evaluate user feedback Recommend and execute improvements Create technical documentation for reference and reporting</string>
    <string name="cinematographer">Why Is Cinematography Important To Filmmaking? Much of the impact of a film or television show is visual. Cinematography represents that visual aspect, whether through the camera and lens choice, angle width, aspect ratio, or other visual elements. The impact of certain shots also plays a significant role in the overall feel of a film. For example, an extremely wide shot places the subject in a more vulnerable position, while a medium shot helps the audience feel like they are part of the conversation. The size of the shot restricts how much of the scene the audience can see.</string>
</resources>